

Stephanie Duffieux

WEB DEVELOPER | GRAPHIC DESIGNER







2 0420 579 085

Key Skills

- Web Development
- Graphic Design, Web Design
- Customer Service
- Stakeholder engagement
- High level administrative and project support.

Technical Proficiency

Tech Stack:

- React (JavaScript & TypeScript)
- Vue.is
- Ruby on Rails
- HTML
- CSS, SASS, Boostrap
- PostgreSQL
- Git, GitHub
- Visual Studio Code
- Wordpress (Elementor | Avada)

Applications:

- Adobe Creative Suite:
 Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator,
 Adobe XD
- Microsoft Office Suite

Capability Statement:

Enthusiastic junior developer and creative graphic designer, making a conscious choice to transition into tech and kick start a career in Software Engineering.

Qualified Graphic Designer with over 4 years experience, specialising in multimedia marketing, digital and print design. Extensive knowledge of the Adobe Creative Suite (InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Adobe XD), and Wordpress using Elementor and Avada.

Education & Qualifications:

- Diploma in Information Technology (graduating Aug 2020).
 Coder Academy, Brisbane QLD
- Diploma in Graphic Design, 2012.
 Martin College of Business, Technology & Design, Brisbane QLD
- Foundation & Advanced Executive Assistants Training, 2017
 Professional Development Training, Brisbane QLD
- French Baccalaureate, 2001. Lycée Laperouse, New-Caledonia

Industry and Personal Skills:

- Good knowledge of front-end and back-end development (HTML, CSS, Ruby on Rails, MERN Stack, Vue.js, PostgreSQL).
- Ability to adapt to new programming languages.
- Excellent knowledge in Graphic Design & Web Design.
- Strong team player and ability to work individually.
- Excellent work ethic and upholding a strict level of confidentiality.
- High level of organisational skills and precise attention to detail.
- Reliable and quick learner, ability to multi task and meet deadlines.

Latest Project Links:

(**Also available on Github** - https://github.com/Beedeeboom)

D'Artiste
Portfolio Website
For-ummm
Youneek

Ruby on Rails Marketplace Application

HTML & CSS

Ruby on Rails Application (Team Hackathon)

| Ruby Terminal Application

Work Experience:

Junior Full Stack Developer

Feb 2020 - Current | Coder Academy, Brisbane

- Build a Terminal application using the Ruby programming language.
- Create a personal portfolio website using HTML and CSS.
- Participate in a team Hackathon to build a Ruby on Rails application (front-end developer role within team).
- Build a two sided marketplace application with Ruby on Rails and use PostgreSQL for database management.
- Build applications using MERN Stack or Vue.js (JavaScript | TypeScript).
- Create full documentation on all application and website projects.
- Regularly commit all work to remote repositories using GitHub and use Git for team work collaboration.

Freelance Graphic Designer

Oct 2019 - Current | Luova Design Solutions, Brisbane - www.luovadesignsolutions.com.au

- Provide graphic and web design solutions for start ups and small businesses.
- Services include logo design, brand identity, web design and website development using Wordpress, design of social media images, brochures, business cards and custom designs to suit client needs.

Executive Assistant / Graphic Designer

2017 - 2019 | Xplore Resources Pty Ltd, Brisbane

- Wordpress website development, design and maintenance for various clients and business partners.
- Manage all graphic design duties including the design of promotional materials for large mining events.
- Professionally design ASX Announcements and presentations for the Geology Department.
- Design and layout of all content for large mining tender submissions (300-500 pages) within tight deadlines.
- Logo and brand identity design for various clients and business partners.
- Provide high level administration support to the CEO, including diary management, agenda preparation, minute taking, coordinate executive communications, preparation of presentations.

Customer Account Manager

2015 - 2017 | APN / News Corp, Yandina Qld

- Ensure timely and accurate completion of all administrative duties including customer account management.
- Communicate with internal and external stakeholders to ensure customer needs are met.
- Coordinate and manage issues as they arise in relation to customers and communicate with all key stakeholders.
- Provide support to the sales team and contribute to the development and maintenance of client relationships.
- Develop dynamic and effective working relationships with external customers, business unit heads, team leaders and team members.

Customer Service Officer / Graphic Designer (Bi-Lingual French & English)

2013-2015 | Mail Marketing & Telemarketing Solutions Pty Ltd, Brisbane

- Assist the arts & production department in designing brochures using the Adobe Creative Suite.
- Provide administrative support to the Customer Service department and assist in daily banking, data entry, mail room duties and proof reading of various translated documents English to French.
- Provide a high level of customer service to international clients (English and French).

Work Experience:

Customer Service Officer / Personal Assistant to CEO

2009-2011 | Pacific Air Cargo Pty Ltd, Brisbane

- Manage all bookkeeping duties, accounts receivables / payables, invoicing.
- Provide personal assistance to the CEO, diary management, coordinate meetings and travel arrangements.
- Handle international air and sea shipments promptly and provide excellent customer service.

Customer Service & Freight Officer

2007-2009 | Aircalin, New-Caledonia (International Airline)

- Provide excellent customer service to new and existing clients.
- Perform administrative and international air freight duties for exports of general cargo, dangerous goods, perishables and live animals.
- Ensure all cargo packed and declared according to strict government and international legislations and regulations.

Customer Service & Freight Officer

2003-2007 | Socatrans International Freight Forwarding Pty Ltd, New-Caledonia

- Provide excellent customer service and high level administrative support including account duties, invoicing, preparation of quotes, accounts receivables/payables and maintain an accurate filing system.
- Ensure completion all freight related documentation, whilst coordinating international air and sea freight duties for imports and exports of general and dangerous goods.
- Manage daily routing and tracking of all air and sea freight, imports and exports.

Administration & Customer Service Officer

2000-2003 | Groupama Gan France Insurance, New-Caledonia

- Perform all reception and front desk customer service duties.
- Provide assistance with invoicing, preparation of quotes, account duties including receivables and payables.
- Handle new client accounts and sales of Car, Home & Contents insurance.

References:

Contact details available on request

Mic Folker (Manager from 2016-2017)

Pre-Press, Operations Manager | APN / News Corp

Sally Hookey (Manager from 2015-2016)

Customer Service Manager | APN / News Corp

Theresa Pretenthaler

Customer Service Manager | MMTS Pty Ltd

Frederic Pierson

Chief Executive Officer | Pacific Air Cargo Pty Ltd